[
    {
        "question": "Which company developes the Android Operating System?",
        "answers": [
            "Microsoft", "Apple", "Google", "IBM"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The main language of Android is what programming language?",
        "answers": [
            "JavaScript", "XML", "C++", "Java"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The main programming language for Android is slowly changing to what?",
        "answers": [
            "C++", "Kotlin", "JavaScript", "Python"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of a screen in Android; that has 1 .xml file and one .java file?",
        "answers": [
            "Action", "Activity", "Alibi", "Alterative" 
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Can we use Processing with Android?",
        "answers": [
            "Yes", "No", "If we try really hard", "" 
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a class in Java?",
        "answers": [
            "A blueprint for creating " 
        ],
        "correct": 
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you think this code will do?<br><br>Intent intent = new Intent(this, SecondActivity.class);<br>startActivity(intent);",
        "answers": [
            "It will close the app.",
            "It will open a version of Google Maps.",
            "It will open an activity called \"SecondActivity\"",
            "It will do nothing at all." 
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "I have a button. Which of the following code will make this button able to be clicked on?",
        "answers": [
            "button.addClicking(clickingFunction);",
            "button.setOnClickListener(new OnClickListener() {...",
            "button.addChangeListener(when clicked do something);",
            "button.setOnClickListener();"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What does \"CPU\" stand for?",
        "answers": [
            "Completely Powerful Unit",
            "Central Park Umbrella",
            "Central Processing Unit",
            "C" 
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How many CPUs do modern computers have?",
        "answers": [
            "One", "At least 100", "Normally 2, 4, or 8", "Modern computers do not have CPUs" 
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is the first CPU so important in Android?",
        "answers": [
            "Becuase the first CPU updates the screen, and changes what we can see.",
            "Because it's the first. And the first is always the most important.",
            "Because the first CPU is the fastest.",
            "The first CPU isn't the most important." 
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answers": [
            "" 
        ],
        "correct": 
    }
]